yellow.com 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

Marchex, Inc., its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively “we” or “Marchex”) respect your privacy. Our purpose in collecting information from you is to help us better understand our user base and to accordingly provide quality service. We will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy statement. Furthermore, we do not specifically target children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect, without parental consent, individually identifiable information from such children. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We may request that an entity applying for an account with Marchex provide us with certain personal information (such as its name, email address, etc.) relevant to our provision of the various services offered on our site. We do not collect any personal information other than that which is specifically and knowingly provided to us. When we request information, we explain how it may be used and give you an opportunity to request that the information not be used for those purposes. Any communications sent from us in the future will include a means to opt out, such as through an opt-out link in the communication.

**Cookies and Other Monitoring Technologies?**

Like most sites, for account management purposes, Marchex may use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about site users. Cookies are data files stored on your computer that identify you as a unique user. In limited instances, we may allow third party business partners to monitor our sites for the purpose of reporting user traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities and to set their cookies on your computer, subject to agreement between such business partner and us and subject to such business partner’s privacy policy. Cookies and related monitoring technologies enable us to track user trends, preferences and patterns. We may also receive and record information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, site(s) you visited and keyword searches you conducted on our site(s). The information helps us provide improved services, including customized advertising.  You can visit our site without using cookies. Most browsers permit users to refuse cookies or to be notified before a cookie is accepted. In addition, you may go to <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> to opt-out of most third party tracking.

**Links to Other Sites?**

The Marchex website contains links to other sites. Those sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content of such sites since we do not control them. 

**With Whom Do We Share Information?**

Marchex may share non-personal and non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. Such non-personally identifiable information may include your IP address, sites(s) you visited and keyword searches you conducted on our site(s). This information may allow such third parties to provide you customized advertising. 

In addition, Marchex may partner with other parties in connection with the various services offered on our site, such as credit card processors or email delivery services. In such instances, we may share limited personal information that is necessary for the third party to provide its services. These companies are prohibited from using this information for any other purpose.

Marchex may also provide personal information when disclosure may be required by law (e.g., subpoenas, search warrants and court orders). We may also determine that such action is reasonably necessary to protect a party’s rights, property, or well-being. This action may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud detection or protection, or in other situations involving suspicious or illegal activities. 

**Business Transfers?**

In the event of a transfer of ownership of Marchex, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, a user’s personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**Consent and Changes to this Privacy Statement?**

By using our site or services, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this privacy statement and consent to our Terms of Use. Additionally, if you are using any of our services, we may also collect and use information in accordance with such service’s applicable Terms and Conditions. Marchex may decide to change this privacy statement from time to time. If and when we do, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Who Can I Ask If I Have Additional Questions?**

Feel free to contact us at any time with any questions you may have regarding our privacy statement. 

Effective October 25, 2010
